maidugan brings to you the most
convenient
insurance claim process by icici lombard
for all your devices for the cashless
claim process
in scenario 1 you have to call icic
lombard's call center
a customer care executive registers your
claim
and the reference number is shared with
you along with the process
info you require a logistic person
visits to pick up the damaged headset
and takes it to asc where engineer
prepares estimate of loss
a payment link is shared with you for
deductible or excess payment
once the payment is received asc repairs
the handset
logistic person delivers it back to you
the necessary claim report documents are
shared with il that is icici lombard and
il settles the amount to the vendor
according to scenario 2 if it is
determined
that the asset is beyond economic repair
that is more than 80 percent of purchase
invoice
engineers report is shared with il and
the logistic person delivers the damage
handset
to il now i'll settles the total loss
claim deducting depreciation
and transfers it to the insurer account
through neft
according to scenario 3 the customer is
informed about the reimbursement mode
when the pin code is non-serviceable
in short gets handset repaired from asc
and uploads claim documents on il
website
they check the documents and share
assessment of laws for consent with the
insured
insured approves assessment through mail
and the loss is settled in insured
accounts within 48 hours
here is a list of documents that you
will need
for the cashless claim and
reimbursements
following is the process showing how the
claim is communicated through several
stages
with the mentioned triggered points for
in short communication
with the maximum possible turnaround
time for the claim processes to go
through
these are the pickup and drop pin codes
with
turnaround times this service is
available
for pickup on 19853 pin codes pan-india
majority of metro location pickup
happens within 24 hours
servify's own fleet on street is on 1310
serviceable pin codes
here is a daily summary sample for your
reference
where most number of claims are
processed in less than a week
or at most a couple of weeks this
is the escalation matrix through this
you can escalate your claims by directly
contacting us
for any issues being faced during your
claim process